<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<i18n baseKey="m.form.document.baseform" lcid="en_GB">
  <key id="document-name">baseform</key>
  <key id="label">title</key>
  <key id="label-help">Form title, displayed on the website</key>
  <key id="description">description</key>
  <key id="description-help">Form description, may be used as the form help text. Displayed on the website as the form header.</key>
  <key id="submitbutton">submit button label</key>
  <key id="submitbutton-help">Submit button label (text displayed on the button at the bottom of the form. Ideally, "Send" or "Submit" is used).</key>
  <key id="markup">layout template</key>
  <key id="markup-help">select the template you wish to apply to the form. The template based on bullet lists is recommended for accessibility reasons.</key>
  <key id="usebacklink">use a return link</key>
  <key id="usebacklink-help">This adds a to link to return to the page visited before coming to this form. This can come in handy when using a form from another module.</key>
  <key id="usecaptcha-help">A CAPTCHA (Completely Automated Public Turing test to Tell Computers and Humans Apart) is a system allowing to ensure that the form is posted by a human (and not a robot) in order to avoid spam. CAPTCHAs generated by RBS Change only contain figures. Warning: using a graphical CAPTCHA goes against accessibility rules.</key>
  <key id="usecaptcha-warning">Warning: using a graphical CAPTCHA goes against accessibility rules.</key>
  <key id="footer">footer text</key>
  <key id="footer-help">Text displayed at the bottom of the form, mainly used to show legal information about the collected data.</key>
  <key id="confirmmessage">confirmation message</key>
  <key id="confirmmessage-help">Confirmation message that is displayed instead of the form after a successful submission. You may use user submitted data with the following syntax: {fieldName}.</key>
  <key id="confirmpage">confirmation page</key>
  <key id="confirmpage-help">confirmation page</key>
  <key id="acknowledgment-notification-label-prefix">[Return receipt]</key>
  <key id="acknowledgment">return receipt</key>
  <key id="acknowledgment-help">Check "yes" to send a return receipt during form submission. For the email to be sent, the form must contain an email type field with the "return receipt recipient" option checked.</key>
  <key id="acknowledgmentnotification">return receipt notification</key>
  <key id="saveresponse">save the responses</key>
  <key id="saveresponse-help">Check "yes" to save the responses to the form.</key>
  <key id="usecaptcha">use a CAPTCHA</key>
</i18n>
